Dawit M. Argaw

Ph.D. Candidate, EE, KAIST

RESEARCH INTERESTS

My research interests lie in the general areas of computer vision and deep learning with a particular focus on video-related topics including video restoration, video synthesis, video editing, long-form video understanding, and multimodal video understanding, but not limited to.

Webpage: https://dawitmureja.github.io

Email: dawitmureja@kaist.ac.kr

EDUCATION

•	KAIST Integrated M.S./Ph.D. in Electrical Engineering; supervised by Prof. In So Kweon	Daejeon, South Korea Sep 2018 - Present
•	KAIST B.S. in Electrical Engineering; GPA: 3.9/4.3 (Magna Cum Laude)	Daejeon, South Korea Sep 2014 - Jul 2018

Publications

- Dawit M. Argaw, Fabian Caba Heilbron, Joon-Young Lee, Markus Woodson, In So Kweon. Long-range Multimodal Pretraining for Movie Understanding. ICCV, 2023.
- Dawit M. Argaw, Fabian Caba Heilbron, Joon-Young Lee, Markus Woodson, In So Kweon. The Anatomy of Video Editing: A Dataset and Benchmark Suite for AI-Assisted Video Editing. ECCV, 2022.
- Dawit M. Argaw, In So Kweon. Long-term Video Frame Interpolation via Feature Propagation. CVPR, 2022.
- Dawit M. Argaw, Junsik Kim, Francois Rameau, In So Kweon. Motion-blurred Video Interpolation and Extrapolation. AAAI, 2021.
- Dawit M. Argaw, Junsik Kim, Francois Rameau, Jae Won Cho, In So Kweon. Optical Flow Estimation from a Single Motion-blurred Image. AAAI, 2021.
- Dawit M. Argaw, Junsik Kim, Francois Rameau, Chaoning Zhang, In So Kweon. Restoration of Video Frames from a Single Blurred Image with Motion Understanding. CVPR-W (Oral), 2021.
- Chaoning Zhang*, Philipp Benz*, **Dawit M. Argaw**, Seokju Lee, Junsik Kim, Francois Rameau, Jean Charles Bazin, In So Kweon. ResNet or DenseNet: Introducing Shortcuts to ResNet. **WACV**, 2021.
- Chaoning Zhang, Francois Rameau, Junsik Kim, **Dawit M. Argaw**, Jean Charles Bazin, In So Kweon. DeePTZ: Deep Self-Calibration for PTZ cameras. **WACV**, 2020.
- Chaoning Zhang, Francois Rameau, Seokju Lee, Junsik Kim, Philipp Benz, **Dawit M. Argaw**, Jean Charles Bazin, In So Kweon. Revisiting Residual Networks with Nonlinear Shortcuts. **BMVC** (**Spotlight**), 2019.
- Dawit M. Argaw*, Malinda Vania*, Deukhee Lee. Automatic spine segmentation from CT images using convolutional neural network via redundant generation of class labels. JCDE, 2019 (*equal contribution).

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

Adobe Research	San Jose, CA
Research Intern, Natural Language Group	May 2023 - Sep 2023
• KAUST Research Intern, Image and Video Understanding (IVUL) Lab	Saudi Arabia (Remote) Nov 2022 - Nov 2023
• Adobe Research Research Intern, Deep Learning Group	San Jose, CA (Remote) Aug 2021 - Nov 2021
• KAIST Research Assistant, Robotics and Computer Vision (RCV) Lab	Daejeon, South Korea Sep 2018 - Present

Honors and Awards

Best Poster Award	2022
• What is Motion For? (WiMF) Workshop, ECCV	
Outstanding Reviewer Award European Conference on Computer Vision (ECCV)	2022
• Magna Cum Laude KAIST Electrical Engineering Department	2018
• Excellent Research Award KAIST Undergraduate Research Participation (URP)	2017
• Dean's List KAIST School of Freshman	2015

ACADEMIC SERVICES

- $\bullet \quad \textbf{Reviewer: CVPR (2021, 2022, 2023), ICCV (2021, 2023), ECCV 2022, BMVC (2022, 2023), NeurIPS 2023, TPAMI } \\$
- Student Volunteer: ICLR 2020, ICML 2020, NeurIPS 2020

References

• Prof. In So Kweon

Professor, School of Electrical Engineering, KAIST

Relationship: M.S. and Ph.D. advisor

Email: iskweon77@kaist.ac.kr

• Dr. Fabian Caba Heilbron

Research Scientist, Adobe Research

Relationship: Internship mentor and collaborator

Email: caba@adobe.com

• Dr. Joon-Young Lee

Senior Research Scientist, Adobe Research

Relationship: Internship mentor and collaborator

Email: jolee@adobe.com